《絕命律師》前情提要
Previously on AMC's "Better Call Saul"...
我想知道你的策略
I'm curious about your strategy.
我不會因爲你弟弟也是律師
I don't intend to take it easy on your brother
- 就對他手下留情 - 這是當然
- just because he's a lawyer. - Of course not.
訴前轉移是查克的主意
The PPD was Chuck's idea.
- 你打算怎麽做 - 其實他只想吊銷我的律師執照
- What are you gonna do? - He just wants my law license.
我不會讓你獨自面對這場戰鬥
I'm not gonna let you fight this on your own.
- 我的手表 - 讓我來吧
- My watch. - Allow me.
赫克托是你的競爭對手
Hector's your competition.
他這時候死掉對我沒啥好處
It's not in my interest for him to die at this time.
你是想破壞他的供應鏈
You want to disrupt his supply line.
我不會阻攔你
I would not stand in your way.
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     杏仁斯嘉麗  克里斯  吃冰棒
翻譯     十月   joy_bwl   Eunice
校對     喃喃  克里斯
時間軸     念念 今 大蔥
后期      蠟筆小新的眉毛  8T
總監      喃喃
你回來了
赫克托
埃拉迪奧
好  告訴我  你有什么大新聞
我收購了一家公司
是嘛
什么公司
冰淇淋
米卻肯州一家不錯的工廠
這是希梅內斯  他們的司機
移民局每次都讓他輕松通關
埃拉迪奧  很榮幸...
蠢貨  沒跟你說話就不許開口
希梅內斯
很高興認識你
告訴我  你肯定不會帶著我們的貨跑了
不會  絕對不會
不不不
開玩笑而已
但對這個人你最好小心點  規矩點
因為他不會給人第二次機會
明白嗎
還有什么
阿爾布開克的一家冰淇淋店
以你命名的
"眨眼的希臘人"
那是什么
這是什么  是我嗎
美味小伙
他在眨眼呢
希梅內斯  你覺得怎么樣
這玩意像我嗎
我不覺得
當然不了
因為它太胖了  是吧
是
-肉嘟嘟的  我可沒那么胖  -對
胖乎乎的
只有這個玩具嗎
我喜歡
繼續...
博爾薩
你個混蛋
埃拉迪奧  見到你真是太高興了
好啊  好啊
赫克托
博爾薩
你帶來什么了
沒什么
包裝真精美
T恤
洛博羅炸雞店
很棒  博爾薩  看啊  赫克托
洛博羅炸雞店[炸雞兄弟]
更像是屁股兄弟
這邊
這是什么
放那邊
古斯塔沃讓我代他問好
僅僅一個月就這么多
他是個經銷天才
看到沒  赫克托
整整齊齊
從現在起  所有人都必須這樣把錢帶來
不要再用橡皮筋了
他本想親自過來問候你
他保證不久就會過來
讓他安心待著吧
繼續做他的事
你怎么看  赫克托  看看古斯塔沃給我們的
真了不起  是不是
還湊合
某人似乎有點嫉妒了啊
關于赫克托你有什么意見  美味小伙
不
美味小伙告訴我  古斯塔沃的生意比你的大
別那樣
不  求你說點好聽的  美味小伙
什么  什么
是啊
你看
美味小伙說你帶來的很可愛
怎么  "可愛"這個詞你還不滿意嗎
赫克托你太嚴肅了  嚴肅過頭了
這兒都是朋友
走吧
北邊還有很多生意等你做呢
過來吧
那么
我們吃午飯吧
為你的小生意喝一杯
掙得真不少  不是嗎
這衣服不錯
正合身
進去  進去
赫克托
你來嗎
別羞辱他
你看什么看
絕命律師
第三季 第四集
眨眼的希臘人
緝毒局
證據
爸
Pop?
親愛的
Hey, honey.
差點沒認出來這號碼
Almost didn't recognize the number.
對不起
I'm sorry.
他們改了我的輪班時間
They changed my hours up at work.
我還在適應
I'm still gettin' used to it.
你們兩個怎么樣
How are you two?
我們很好
We're great.
還順利嗎
Did it go okay?
對  多虧了你找的那幾個搬運工
Yeah, yeah, thanks to those movers you got.
我在一旁看著就行
All I had to do was watch.
爸  這間房子...
And, Pop, this house...
還行嗎
It's good?
好極了
It's great.
凱莉喜歡新學校
Kaylee loves her new school.
鄰居都很友善
The neighborhood's friendly.
我們感覺很安全
We feel safe.
那就好
That's good.
麥克  我不知道該怎么感謝你
Mike, I don't know how to thank you.
不必客氣
Well, you don't hafta.
我很高興你喜歡
I'm just glad you're enjoying it.
你想過來吃晚飯嗎
Do you want to come over for dinner?
今晚
Tonight?
對  我在做千層面  有好多呢
Sure. I'm making lasagna. There'll be plenty.
你真貼心  但我不想麻煩你
Well, that's very sweet, but I don't want to put you out.
爺爺  來吧
Pop-pop, come over!
有人著急想見你呢
There's someone here who wants to see you.
冰淇淋來了
Ice cream!
她在打盹嗎
Oh, is she snoozing?
快了
Close.
冰淇淋
Ice cream?
我就該放著不管的
I shoulda let well enough alone.
我不明白
Well, I can't understand it.
地圖上說
According to the map,
我們走的是捷徑才對
we were supposed to be taking a shortcut.
不用了
I'm good.
-你確定  -對
- You sure? - Yeh.
我可以把他那份吃掉
I'll have his.
這可不行
Oh, I don't think so.
也許我們可以搭個車
Maybe we can get a lift.
怎么回事
Hey! What's the matter?
卡車附近有幾個人
There's some guys hanging around the truck.
空襲哨兵嗎
Air raid wardens?
不  這些人長得很奇怪
No, these is funny-lookin' guys.
什么叫"長得很奇怪"
What do you mean "Funny-lookin'"?
奇怪  就像魚一樣
I mean funny-lookin', like fish.
你在開玩笑嗎  什么叫"像魚一樣"
Who are you kidding? What do you mean "Like fish"?
他們有鱗片
They got scales.
-在哪兒  -全身都是
- Where? - All over 'em!
你沒事吧
You okay?
對  我沒事
Oh, yeah, I'm -- I'm fine.
他們從飛碟上下來的  人造衛星
They're off a flyin' saucer, off a sputnik.
看  他們看見我們了
Ohh, look! They've seen us!
我們趕緊走
Let's get outta here!
他們是從外太空來的  從飛碟下來的
They're from outer space. They're off a flying saucer!
歡迎光臨洛博羅炸雞  想要點什么
Welcome to Los Pollos Hermanos. May I take your order?
你老板在哪兒
Tu jefe esta aqui?
在哪兒
Donde esta?
男洗手間在左邊
Uh, men's room is over there on the left.
-先生...  -蠢貨  我要見你老板
- Sir, if -- - Cabron, I need to see your boss.
好吧  我是經理助理
Okay. Well, I'm -- I'm the assistant manager.
經理今天不在
The manager's actually not here today.
不是經理  是老板
Not the manager -- the boss.
-你是說弗林先生  -弗林先生
- You mean Mr. Fring? - Mr. Fring.
好吧  他暫時不在
O-Okay, well, he's not here at the moment.
我肯定也能幫到您
Uh, I'm sure I could help you with whatever you need.
我要找弗林
I need Fring.
我說了  他不在
Well, like I said, he's not here,
我不知道他什么時候能回來
uh, and I don't really know when he'll be back.
我可以捎個信
I can -- I can take a message.
我等著
I'll wait.
你...你不必這樣
You -- you don't have to do that.
我很樂意給您捎個信
I'd be happy to take a message.
弗林先生肯定不想讓您這樣等著
Uh, I'm sure Mr. Fring wouldn't want to keep you waiting.
先生  如果你不介意
Uh, okay, sir, if you -- if you don't mind,
后面還有其他顧客
there are oth-- there are other customers.
不好意思
Uh, s-sorry about that.
歡迎光臨洛博羅炸雞  想要點什么
Welcome to Los Pollos Hermanos. Uh, may I take your order?
我要個十二塊炸雞桶裝套餐
Yeah, can I get a 12-piece bucket,
大份薯條  還有...
uh, with jumbo fries and, uh...
-您要十二塊桶  -對  十二塊
- You said the 12-piece? - Yeah, the 12-piece.
好的
Uh-huh. Okay.
抱歉  先生
Uh, excuse me, sir.
這里不能抽雪茄
You can't light that in here.
先生
Sir!
這里不能抽煙
There's no smoking on the premises.
拜托  先生  看那個標識
Please, sir, look -- look at the signs.
禁止吸煙
No fumar.
不可以  這違反了衛生條例
You can't. That's -- It's a -- It's a health-code violation.
-先生  只有員工才能進來  -我們得走了
- Uh, sir, it's employees only. - We have to go, okay? Let's go.
先生
Sir!
先生  你不能進來
Sir, you're not allowed back here.
古斯·弗林是當地工商界的中流砥柱
Gus Fring is a pillar of our local business community,
不光是因為給我們發旅行彩券
and not just for underwriting our travel raffle,
更因為做出城里最棒的炸雞
but for making the best damn chicken in town!
-古斯  -謝謝
- Gus. - Thank you.
謝謝
Thank you.
先生們  女士們
Well, uh, gentlemen, ladies,
我希望永遠都不需要各位的服務
I-I hope to never need your services --
無意冒犯  但是如果需要
I mean, no offense -- but if I ever did,
很高興...
it's good to know that --
喂
Yes?
我這就來
I'll be right there.
大家都回家吧
I want you all to go home now.
給大家算全勤
You will be compensated for your full shifts.
明天正常上班
Normal schedule tomorrow.
快走吧
Go now.
今天不營業了
We are closed for today.
弗林先生  你確定要和這些人一起留下嗎
Mr. Fring, y-you sure you want to be left with these guys?
沒事的  萊爾  回家吧
I'm fine, Lyle. You go home.
要我打給誰嗎
Should I call someone?
不用
No.
沒有這個必要  真的
That will not be necessary. Truly.
你確定
Are you sure?
照我說的做吧
Please do as I ask.
明天見
I'll see you tomorrow.
他在辦公室里
He's waiting in the office.
我知道他在哪
I know where he is.
赫克托
Don Hector.
你也太慢了
Took you long enough.
赫克托
Don Hector,
我的生意屬于集團性質
Mine is a cartel business,
但那也是我的生意
but it is mine.
而且是合法的
And it is legitimate.
我的雇員都是普通老百姓
My employees are civilians.
你今天的行為威脅到了他們的生命
Your actions here today have endangered them,
威脅了我的利益  以及集團中的其他人
my interests, and those of the cartel.
我就是集團
I am the cartel.
從現在起  你給我運貨
And from now on, you are my mule.
你要替我向北方運貨
You are going to bring my product north.
該死
Mierda.
我知道你的運輸線出了問題
I understand that your supply line has been compromised,
這很不幸
and this is most unfortunate.
但是  我的卡車已經達到了最大容量
However, my trucks are already at maximum capacity.
給我騰地方
Make room.
赫克托
Don Hector,
你要明白  我是對胡安·博爾薩負責
you must understand that I answer to Juan Bolsa.
我想對博爾薩哭訴  那就去
You want to cry to Bolsa, cry to Bolsa.
或者那該死的埃拉迪奧
Or, hell, Eladio.
增加貨物量會威脅
Adding more product will threaten
整條產業鏈的可靠度
the reliability of the entire operation.
我可否問下  埃拉迪奧允許此事嗎
May I ask -- did Don Eladio approve this?
我允許了
I approve this.
你去做就是
You're doin' it.
不讓我出去嗎
You gonna let me out of here?
喂
Hello?
告訴他我們扯平了
Tell him we're square.
什么
What?
不
No.
不好意思  各位
Excuse me, everyone.
能占用大家一點時間  請大家過來一下嗎
Could you all please take a moment and join me out here?
過來吧
Please, come.
到這里來
Come, come, come.
我想
I would, uh,
我想對你們道歉
I would like to apologize to each and every one of you
為昨天你們不得不忍受那些人的行為而道歉
who, yesterday, had to endure the behavior of those men.
那是不可接受的
It was unacceptable.
盡管當時情況危急
Despite the difficult circumstances,
但你們仍表現出色
you all acquitted yourselves impeccably.
因此  如果有任何人受到了精神創傷
That said, if any of you wish to seek counseling
想要尋求心理咨詢
due to lingering trauma,
可以私下跟我說  我會安排
speak with me privately, and it will be arranged.
還有  你們會增加二十四小時的加班
Also, you will all be receiving 24 hours of overtime,
因為我確信  你們回到家之后
as I am sure, in one way or another,
或多或少還受到這次事件的影響
each of you brought this incident home with you.
你說  萊爾
Uh, yes, Lyle?
弗林先生  那些人是誰
Mr. Fring, uh... who were those guys?
你們其中的一些人知道  很多年前
Well, some of you know, that many years ago,
我在米卻肯州開了第一家洛博羅炸雞店
I opened my first Los Pollos Hermanos in Michoacán.
開店后不久
Shortly thereafter,
那些人就出現了
those same men showed up.
他們想要錢
They wanted money.
而我...
And I-I am --
我很慚愧  我給了他們
I'm ashamed to say that I paid them.
在那種地方  在那個年代
You see, in that place, at that time,
如果想繼續做生意  我就別無選擇
if I wished to conduct my business...I had no choice.
但是昨天...
but yesterday...
昨天  他們來到了這里
yesterday, they came here.
這里
Here.
他們嚇到了我的客人
They intimidated my customers.
威脅了我的員工
They threatened my employees.
再一次地
And, again,
他們又來要錢了
they wanted money.
我的朋友們  我必須承認
Now, my friends, I-I must confess
我差點就給了他們
that I almost gave them what they wanted.
但是突然  我想  "不
But then, I thought, "No.
不
No.
這里是美國"
This is America."
在這里  正直的人沒有理由害怕
Here, the righteous have no reason to fear.
在這里  那些人沒有力量
Here, those men have no power.
當他們發現我并不怕他們時
And when they saw that I had no fear of them,
他們就像懦夫一樣溜走了
they ran like the cowards they are.
穿過邊境回去了
Back across the border.
再也不會回來
They will not return.
我們會繼續前進
We will move on from this.
朋友們
My friends,
我向你們保證...
I promise you...
只要團結一致  我們一定會繁榮昌盛
that together, we will prosper.
說得太好了
All right.
喂  你好  我還在聽
Yes, hi. I'm still here.
真的嗎  你確定
Really? Uh, are you sure?
當然  明白
Sure. Gotcha.
很抱歉打攪到您
Sorry for bothering you.
我打電話來是因為我們和你們有個預約
I'm calling because we had an appointment with you guys for,
我想想  星期三
I think, Wednesday?
老實告訴你
I'll be honest with you --
我寫的東西我自己都看不懂
I can barely read my own darn handwriting.
我的錯
My mistake.
好吧  祝你今天過得愉快
Okay. Have a nice day.
你好  我打來是想確認一下
Hello. I'm calling to confirm an appointment
和查爾斯·麥吉爾的預約
for Charles McGill.
對  在圣克里斯托瓦爾路215號
Yes, it's 215 San Cristobal Road --
麥吉爾  開頭字母是"M"
McGill, with an "M."
修門
A door?
好吧
Okay.
我以為是你們
I thought it was you guys.
我可能搞錯了
Guess I was wrong.
還是謝謝了
Thanks, anyway.
你好  我打來是為了
Hi! I'm calling about
和查爾斯·麥吉爾的一個預約
an appointment for Charles McGill.
我打來就是為了這個
Well, that's why I'm calling.
我想就是這星期了  但是...
I think it's for this week, but --
幸好我的腦袋還在原位  對嗎
Good thing my head's attached to my neck right?
圣克里斯托瓦爾  沒錯
San Cristobal -- that's right.
對  就是這個  明天兩點半
Yes, that's it! 2:30 tomorrow.
太好了
Great!
我們得取消這次預約
So, uh, we're gonna need to cancel that.
是的
Yeah.
我會的
I will.
謝謝你  再見
Thank you. Bye.
明天
馬丁勤雜修理店
可憐的福瑞斯基
Poor Frisky.
波美拉尼亞人比較難搞  那頭發
Mm. Pomeranians can be difficult -- all that hair.
我知道
I know.
那瓦蘭斯夫人  周四十一點半可以嗎
So, Mrs. Vallance, does Thursday 11:30 work?
對
That's right.
不是吧
No.
真的
Really?
馬丁勤雜修理店  明天兩點半
Martin's Handyman and Repair -- 2:30 tomorrow.
謝謝
Thank you.
你打了多少電話才試出來的
How many calls did that take?
數不清了  寫好了嗎
I lost track. Is that it?
是的  我快做完了
Yeah. I'm nearly done.
我準備打悔過牌
I'm just giving it a remorse pass.
悔過很重要
Well, remorse is important.
"毀壞財產"
"Destroyed property."
我會寫"損壞"了受害者的財產
I'd try "Damaged" the victim's property
而不是"毀壞"財產
instead of "Destroyed" property.
看看這樣能不能好點
See if you can't get away with that.
好
Yeah.
好了
Boom.
這樣挺好的
That's nice.
順便告訴你  我是真心的
I mean it, by the way.
什么
What?
謝謝你
Thank you.
說真的
Seriously.
說真的  不客氣
You're welcome seriously.
我要接著忙了
I better get back to it.
好
Yeah.
你是不是...
Are you...?
你確定這個人能行嗎
You're absolutely sure you got the right guy for this?
高手中的高手
The crème de la crème.
馬丁修理店
Martin's Repair?
是的  麥吉爾先生
Yeah. Mr. McGill?
下午好
Good afternoon.
麻煩把鞋擦一下
If you don't mind wiping your shoes?
這邊走
It's this way.
當心  當心這邊的臺階
Mind -- Mind the step here.
如你所見  門框貼上了木板
Uh, as you'll see, the frame is boarded over,
但是門還是完好的
but the, uh, the door itself is intact.
主要是門側柱和門框壓條壞了
The damage is mainly to the doorjamb and the casing.
這邊還有一級臺階
There's another step up here.
有人闖進來了嗎
Break-in?
是的
That's right.
看上去是為了你的銅線
Went after your copper wire, from the look of it.
想當年  記得嗎
There was a time -- remember? --
我們可以不用鎖門
when we could leave our doors unlocked.
當然記得
I certainly do.
這個...
Well...
我在哪兒接電源
Where do I plug in?
不能插電
You don't.
-不能嗎  -不行
- No? - No.
你難道不能...
Didn't you --
我覺得我的助理已經和你們說得很清楚了
I believe my assistant was very clear with your dispatcher --
不能用電
no electricity,
原因已經解釋得夠詳細了
due to a condition that was explained in some detail.
沒問題
No problem.
幸好我給電池充了電
Good thing I charged my battery.
不然我就只能像摩登原始人一樣了
I'd be going at it like Fred Flintstone, otherwise.
很抱歉
I'm sorry!
我以為不會需要任何用電的工具
I understood there would be no power tools of any kind.
什么  螺絲刀和錘子嗎
What? A screwdriver and a hammer?
本來一早上能干完的活兒要我弄兩天
Turns a morning job into two days
還得賠上止痛膏藥嗎
with me, myself, and Bengay.
但是  還是你說了算
But...it's your call.
我覺得...
I suppose...
好吧  如果...
Very well, if --
你看起來很快就能搞完
You seem to be making fast work of it.
很好  很好
That's good. That's good.
好吧  那我就...
Okay, what I'll do, I think, is, uh...
很好
Very good.
太好了
Oh, yeah.
漂亮
Nice.
很好  漂亮
Great. Yep, nice.
我們也許該找個時間討論一下黃金分割法
At some point, we should probably discuss the rule of thirds,
不過這些...
but, otherwise, these, uh...
一疊《金融時報》上放著一盞煤油燈
A gas lantern sitting on a stack of friggin' Financial Times.
這可把來龍去脈都交代清楚了
Now, that tells the whole story.
這些照片都能放到博物館展出了
These are museum quality.
我的朋友  你簡直是偷拍界的大師
You, my friend, are the Ansel Adams of covert photography.
另外那樣東西呢
And that other thing?
你是怎么拿到的
How'd you get it?
從他桌上的地址簿
Address book on his desk.
對哦
Right.
你覺得他怎么樣
So...What'dya think of him?
你可以有話直說  不會得罪我的
I mean, speak freely. You couldn't possibly offend me.
他挺混蛋的  對吧
He's a bit of a prick, right?
無話可說嗎
Nothing?
真的嗎
Seriously?
好吧
All right.
跟這人聊不了八卦
Can't even dish the dirt with this guy.
我們的合作不是結束了嗎
Isn't our business concluded?
是的  扯平了
Yeah, even Steven.
你的確把門修好了吧
I mean, you did fix the door, right?
是的
Yeah.
你修得還不錯吧
Y-You did a reasonably good job of it?
-否則  他會...  -他不會投訴的
- Because, otherwise, he'll be -- - He won't be grumbling to anyone.
那就行了
That's all I'm asking.
我修得很好
I did it right.
謝謝
Thank you.
終于有一次是修東西了
Nice to fix something for once.
如果你真那么想
Hell, if that's how you feel,
我辦公室還有個漏水的馬桶呢
I got a leaky toilet back at the office.
好了
All right.
如果你以后需要我幫忙...
If you ever need anything from my end...
再見
Hasta luego.
《能工巧匠》
我們能談談嗎
May we talk?
你可以把車停到那邊
You can park it over there.
你把我們說好的酬勞退回來了
You sent back the payment we agreed upon.
我做那些事不是為了你
What I did, I didn't do for you.
那個男人
The man.
那個因為幫助貨車司機而被殺的人
The one killed for helping the truck driver.
容我多嘴
If I may make an observation...
也許你是想彌補過錯
Perhaps you are trying to correct something
一些無法挽回的事
which cannot be corrected.
我做這種事不是為了錢
It's not the kind of thing I want to take money for.
但事實仍然是  你的行為令我受益
But the fact remains that your actions
多到你無法想象
benefited me more than you can know.
那是你的事
That's your business.
我不用再煩惱塞拉曼加的事  就夠了
I'm just glad to have Salamanca out of my head.
也許將來...
Well, perhaps, in the future...
你會考慮為我工作
you will consider working for me.
也許吧
Could be.
得看具體工作內容
That'd depend on the work.
你想知道
Would you care to know
我為什么阻止你殺赫克托嗎
why I stopped you from killing Hector?
如你所說  那對你沒好處
Like you said -- it wasn't in your interest.
被一槍爆頭對他來說太仁慈了
A bullet to the head would have been far too humane.
吉米
Jimmy.
霍華德
Howard.
吉米
Jimmy.
霍華德
Howard.
金
Kim.
查克
Chuck.
金
Kim.
下午好
Good afternoon.
很好
Good.
麥吉爾先生  這樣可以嗎
Mr. McGill, does this work for you?
也只能這樣了  謝謝
It'll have to do. Thank you.
各位都把手機等電子產品
I assume everyone left their cellphones
-放到接待處了吧  -是的
- and so on at reception. - Yes, indeed.
如果你要休息一下或有其他需求  請告訴我
And you'll let me know if you need a break or anything else?
我會的  謝謝  海女士
I will. Thank you, Ms. Hay.
其實
You know...
我跟我先生說起過你的情況
I was actually speaking to my husband about your condition.
是嗎
Oh, yes?
我以前有個姨媽  她已經過世了
I had an aunt. She's no longer with us.
她每周日都到教堂去
She went to church every Sunday,
可是當唱詩班的孩子開始唱歌
but when the boys' choir sang,
她就必須離開
she would absolutely have to leave.
他們聲音的頻率
Something about the frequency of their voices
讓她受不了
really did a number on her.
-那太可惜了  -確實
- Well, that is a shame. - Indeed.
好了
All right.
我們開始吧
Let's get down to it.
我們今天要落實
We are here to finalize
詹姆斯·摩根·麥吉爾的訴前轉移
the Pre-Prosecution Diversion for James Morgan McGill.
代理被轉移人的是金柏莉·韋克斯勒女士
Representing the divertee, Ms. Kimberly Wexler.
詹姆斯·麥吉爾先生簽了一份協議
Mr. James McGill has signed a contract
在法定訴訟時效內
waiving his rights to a speedy trial
放棄快速審判和案件陳述的權利
and presentment of his case within the statute of limitations.
協議條款要求你  詹姆斯
The terms of the deal are for you, James,
在未來十二個月內  于每月第二個周一
to report to your Pre-Prosecution Service Officer
到阿爾布開克地檢辦公室
at the Albuquerque District Attorney's Office
向訴前事務官報到
on the second Monday of every month for the next 12 months.
屆時會分配社區服務時長
Community service hours will be assigned.
你必須保持合法就業
You must maintain lawful employment.
只能和守法公民來往
Must only associate with law-abiding citizens.
你的委托人是否明白
Your client understands that,
如果他違反協議條款
if he violates the terms of the agreement
或者因違法被捕
or is arrested for any infraction,
他在此供認的罪名
the crimes to which he has confessed here
將連同新的罪名一起
will be prosecuted to the full extent of the law,
依法受到最大限度的追訴
in addition to any new charges?
他明白
He understands.
我必須告知你  麥吉爾先生
And I must inform you, Mr. McGill,
作為一名律師及律師協會成員
as an officer of the court and member of the bar,
你的供詞將會被提交給
your confession will be referred
新墨西哥律師協會
to the New Mexico Bar Association.
好了  我這里有份你的陳述
Okay. I have your statement here.
有誰事先讀過了嗎
Has everyone had a chance to read it?
有什么評論或想法
Comments? Thoughts?
第二頁上說  他"損壞了被害人的財產"
Actually, page 2, he "Damaged the victim's property."
可不可以更準確地改成
Would it not be more accurate to say
"毀壞了一盤錄音帶"
"Destroyed a cassette tape"?
抱歉  錄音帶難道不是他的財產嗎
I'm sorry. Wasn't the cassette tape his property?
-當然是  -那說他損壞了
- Of course it was. - Then it seems entirely accurate to say
被害人的財產十分準確
he damaged the victim's property.
為什么含糊其辭
Why be vague?
并且"損壞"不能說明其無法挽回的后果
And "Damaged" doesn't reflect its irrevocable condition --
好  改成"損壞了被害人的私人物品"
Fine. "Damaged property belonging to the victim."
是錄音帶
It was a cassette tape.
事實就是如此  不是茶杯  或者椅子
That's what it was -- not a teacup, not a chair --
-是一盤錄音帶  -沒錯
- a cassette tape. - Yeah.
改成"毀壞私人財產"怎么樣
How about "Destroyed item of personal property"?
行
All right.
我們建議改成"毀壞私人財產"
Uh, we'd suggest "Destroyed item of personal property."
韋克斯勒小姐
Ms. Wexler?
無異議
Works for us.
那我是不是該修改一下  還是...
Shall I change it, or...?
請便
If you would.
"毀壞私人財產"
"Destroyed item of personal property."
好了
There.
請您簽上姓名的首字母
Can you initial it, please?
"JMM"  簽好了
"JMM." Initialed.
查爾斯  您對您弟弟的陳述還有其他
Charles, was there anything else you found wanting
欠缺的地方嗎
in your brother's statement?
沒有了
No.
我們很滿意  謝謝您
We're satisfied. Thank you.
好  我們完事了吧
All right. So, we're all set.
不  還沒完  麥吉爾先生
No, not all set, Mr. McGill.
你哥哥或許滿意了  但我還沒有
Your brother may be satisfied, but I am not.
你寫的供詞還說過得去
The confession you've written is adequate,
但老實說  我覺得缺少悔意
but, frankly, I-I sense a lack of remorse.
我希望您有所行動  比如道個歉
And I, for one, would like to hear an apology.
這是查爾斯最起碼應得的
Charles deserves at least that much.
現在嗎
Now?
是的  麥吉爾先生  現在
Yes, Mr. McGill, now.
好吧
Okay.
我錯了
I was wrong.
麥吉爾先生  說的時候能直視你哥哥嗎
Mr. McGill, could you at least look your brother in the eye?
查克  我真的很抱歉
Chuck... I'm very sorry.
我發了脾氣  做了一些事...
I lost my temper, and I did some things --
很多讓我后悔不已的事
so many things that I regret.
我不應該砸壞你的門
I shouldn't have broken down your door.
不管我有多么生氣
Doesn't matter how I was provoked.
都不應該那樣做
I-I shouldn't have done that.
我不會為此或者自己所說的話找借口
There's no excuse for that. Or for the things that I said.
我非常懊悔
I regret it all,
后悔到你完全無法想象
all of it more than you can imagine,
因為...
because...
你是我的哥哥
'cause you're my brother,
沒人應該那樣對待自己的兄弟
and no one should treat his own brother like that.
永遠不會
Not ever.
可以嗎
Okay?
好的
All right, then.
我們接下來談談賠償問題
On to the matter of restitution.
麥吉爾先生  根據協議書規定
Mr. McGill, according to your agreement,
您有兩周時間賠償您的哥哥
you have two weeks to pay your brother back.
我現在就能賠  如果可以的話
I would like to pay up now, if I may.
可以
You may.
賠償金額共計三百二十一美元
The amount is $321.
海女士  我很抱歉
Uh, Ms. Hay. I'm sorry.
這個數字沒有囊括所有的金額
That figure doesn't represent a full accounting.
是嗎
Oh, no?
賠償金額應該是323.98美元
I believe the correct amount is $323.98.
其中包括那盤...
That includes the cassette tape...
被毀壞的錄音帶
which was destroyed.
好  謝謝您
Good. Thank you.
323.98美元  包括錄音帶
$323.98, including the cassette tape.
地方檢察官辦公室
訴前轉移緩刑部門
把你送回家怎么樣
What do you say we get you home?
霍華德  查克
Howard. Chuck.
關于聽證會我得警告你們
I'm putting you both on notice regarding the bar hearing.
第一件  我會提交對錄音的查禁請求
The first thing, I'm filing a motion to suppress that tape.
你是說  吉米毀掉的那盤錄音
The tape that Jimmy destroyed, you mean?
我們就別兜圈子了吧
How about we stop with the games?
你們肯定還有副本
There's no way there isn't a duplicate.
是嗎
Really?
絕對還有
Of course there is.
你們早就知道吉米會闖進去
You knew Jimmy was gonna break in.
你們正希望如此
You wanted him to.
你們不會任由他毀掉那盤錄音
There's no way you were gonna let him destroy
僅存的原件  所以肯定復制了副本
the only copy of that tape, so you made a duplicate --
你們一開始就準備好了
it's the first thing you did.
金  披露不是這樣做的
Kim...this is not how we do discovery.
事實上  吉米毀掉了副本
Actually, Jimmy destroyed the duplicate.
沒關系  霍華德
It's fine, Howard.
原件被妥善地保管著
The original is under lock and key,
在適當的時間
and in due time,
會被拿來當做證據
it will be put into evidence for your review.
所以  你想提交動議就提交吧
So, of course, file whatever motions you'd like.
這是你的權利
It's your privilege.
我會的  等著吧
I will. Count on it.
但是  金  你應該知道...
But, Kim, you should be aware --
因為我相信這是你
because I believe this will be
第一次參加紀律聽證會
your first disciplinary hearing --
律師協會所要求的舉證標準
uh, the Bar Association's standard of proof
比你習以為常的那套要仁慈多了
is far more lenient than what you're used to.
撇開動議  那盤錄音帶會被播放的
Motions aside, that tape will be played.
-查克  -好
- Chuck. - Yeah.
再見  金
See you, Kim.
怎么樣
Well?
怎么了
What?
猜對了
Bingo.